复习练习 1-10：个人练习。第一，说明她男朋友更喜欢
Review exercise 110, individual practice. One, indicate that her boyfriend prefers
活的植物，而不是切花。
live plants to cut ones.
她男朋友几乎从不送她花，但他在花园里
Her boyfriend almost never sends her flowers, but he planted a lot in her
种了很多。第二，表示她的姐妹们很关心她的园艺需求。
garden. Two, indicate that her sisters are attentive to her horticultural needs.
第三，说明她男朋友送她的是非鲜花礼物。
3. Indicate that her boyfriend gives her non-floral presents.
她男朋友几乎从不送她花，却送她很多其他
Her boyfriend almost never sends her flowers, but he showers her with other
礼物。第四，表示我的男朋友在送花这方面做得不错。
gifts. 4. Indicate that my boyfriend is good in the flower department.
她男朋友几乎从不送她花，但我的男朋友会。第五，表示她男朋友送花这件事极其罕见。
Her boyfriend almost never sends her flowers, but mine does. 5. Indicate that
她男朋友送花真的很罕见。
it is a true rarity for her boyfriend to send flowers.
她男朋友几乎从不送她花，无论如何都不会。第六，表示他其实还有一点点可能会送花。
Her boyfriend almost never sends her flowers, no matter what. 6. Indicate that
他其实还是有一点点可能会送花。
there's actually a slim chance that he might send flowers.
她男朋友几乎从不送她花，但偶尔
Her boyfriend almost never sends her flowers, but every once in a while he
还是会送。第七，表示她男朋友记得给自己的母亲送花。
does. 7. Indicate that her boyfriend remembers to send flowers to his mother.
她男朋友几乎从不送她花，但他从不会忘记母亲节。
Her boyfriend almost never sends her flowers, but he never forgets Mother's Day.